techxat.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy -

At Techxat.com, we care about the privacy of all readers and subscribers so We have invest a lot in WEB to keep all readers safe. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**What information we collect about you?**

Techxat also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Techxat.com blogs/sites.  
We don’t ask people to Sign Up but if you want to recieve the latest news from website you can Subscribe Us to Click Sign in/Sign Up in Top Header Menu and Techxat will automatically send you news to your Inbox.  
If you are not satisfied with our Service you can Unsubscribe any time. This is free and it will be always.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Techxat uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of Techxat website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Techxat website, with the drawback that certain features of Techxat websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### ADS

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Techxat and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
You can disable our cookies in your browser setting or by an Antivirus.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection

We do not collect any inforamtion from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Website, Products and Services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

##### Will Change the Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy is supossed from time to time, Techxat should encourages visitors to check this page frequently for any changes to Privacy Policy.  
If you are a subscriber you will revieve an email about Privacy Policy.

_Last Update  2016-8-25_

If you have any question about Privacy Policy of Techxat, You can [Contact US](http://techxat.com/contact-us/)
